4K电影 https://4K-m.com 提供
你不冷也没不舒服吧，是吗？
You're not cold or anything, are you?
一切都好吗？
Everything all right?
你在吃药吧？
Are you taking any medication?
嗯？
Hmm?
谢谢你
Thank you
你今早感觉如何？
How are you doing this morning?
昨晚你睡得安稳吗？
Did you have a restful sleep last night?
哦，是的
Oh, yeah
是吗？是的
You did? I did
有梦吗？没
Any dreams? Nope
有时候我们只是不记得自己的梦，你知道吧？
Sometimes we don't remember our dreams, you know?
没错
That's right
我们的确会做梦，但是我们起床后
We do dream, but we don't remember
就不记得了- 是的
when we wake up - NO
但是如果我们在要醒来时
But if we are dreaming some
正在梦着什么，我们就记得那些
just before we wake up, we remember those
没错
That's right
你知道吧
Did you know
一点~额~额~有用的信息
A little, uh uh, useful information
是啊，当我们醒来的时候
Yeah When we wake up
然后说，整个晚上，
and say, The whole night,
我做了什么什么梦
I was dreaming this and that and everything,
这梦最多只有45分钟
it's only 45 minutes maximum
你知道吗？- 对。不，我不知道这些。对
Did you know that? - Yeah. No, I did not. Yeah
所以普通的梦是十分钟或十五分钟
So the ordinary dream is ten or 15 minutes
待会儿见
I'll see you all later
你要去哪里？我要去看我的病人
Where are you going? I'm going to see my patients
测试。测试
Testing. Testing
检查，检查，检查一，二，三
Check, check, check One, two, three
测试。一，二，三
Testing. One, two, three
我们现在在史密斯森林
We are now at Smith's Grove,
呃，康复疗养院
uh, rehabilitation facility
我们今天来这里采访一个病人
We're here today to interview a patient
在过去的40年里被关在这
that's spent the last 40 years in captivity
而且，所有人都说说，他到现在一句话也没讲过
and, by all accounts, has not uttered a word
这个怪物
This monster
下午好下午好
Good afternoon Good afternoon
我是兰博・萨坦博士
I'm Dr. Ranbir Sartain
很高兴终于见到你了
Great to finally meet you
非常感谢你今天抽出时间和我们见面
Thank you so much for taking the time to meet with us today
我们一直期待这个机会
We were hoping to have this opportunity
在他被转移到新医院之前
before he's transferred to the new facility
格拉斯山就不那么好说话了
Glass Hill is far less accommodating
格拉斯山简直就是地狱
Glass Hill is the pit of hell
多年来，他一直被留在这里做研究
For years, he's been kept here to be studied
我想国家已经对从他身上
I suppose the state has lost interest
有人么，救救我啊！求你了！
Somebody, please help me! Please!
拜托，有人么，救命！啊！
Please, somebody, help me! Aah!
啊！任何人！奥斯卡，得了吧
Aah! Anybody! Oscar, come on
求你了，亲爱的上帝！求你了！
Please, dear God! Please!
求...求你了！
Plea... Please!
救我！救我！救我！
Help me! Help me! Help me!
请救我！
Please help me!
奥斯卡！
Oscar!
救命！让我进去！
Help! Let me in!
让我进去！
Let me in!
救命！
Help!
有人！
Somebody!
救命！
Help!
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
有人么！
Somebody!
求你了！
Please!
救命！
Help!
因为我女儿没有打电话
Cause my daughter is not calling
这对你更安全
It's safer for you
她没有发短信来，凯伦，我们进去吧
She's not texting Come on, Karen, let's go inside
每个人都在找你的女儿
Everyone's looking for your daughter
让他们来处理吧所以不管你们谁在
Let them take care of it So whoever you had
找她，显然不能认出她
looking for her is obviously not able to identify her
我们会找到你的女儿今天是万圣节
We're gonna find your daughter It's Halloween
我们会带她来 -这里到处都是孩子
We're gonna bring her here - There are kids everywhere
凯伦，来吧，没有办法
Karen, come on There is no way
凯伦。凯伦她有一套服装，你知道吗？
Karen. Karen She had a costume, you know?
我们需要进屋去，我们能调的人手都来了
We need to go in the house We have everybody available
在过去的40年里，好吗？
In the last 40 years, okay?
亲爱的，如果你让他们做他们的工作，他们会
Honey, if you let 'em do their job, they're gonna
凯伦！
Karen!
深呼吸，如果你愿意，我们可以打电话给你
Just breathe And if you want, we can call
待在车里，医生
Stay in the car, Doctor
你没事吧？深呼吸，亲爱的
You all right? Take deep breaths, sweetheart
他...他在街上好吗
He's... he's down the street Okay
好吧，他回来了。他杀了我的朋友
Okay He's back. He killed my friend
一切都会好起来的。现在没事了
Everything's gonna be all right. It's okay
深呼吸
Take a deep breath
我们会带你回到你妈妈身边，好吗？
We're gonna take you back to your mom, okay?
我是医生。把门锁上
I'm a doctor. Lock your doors
各位，现在回到你们的房子，锁上门
Everybody, get back to your houses now and lock your doors
我们会带你去你妈那儿
We're gonna take you to your mom
不用怕他，不用怕他
Don't worry about him Don't worry about him
现在回到你们的房子里！
Back in your houses now!
你听到警官的话了吗
You heard the officer
这是怎么回事？回到你们的房子里！
What is going on? Back in your houses!
锁上门
Lock your goddamn doors
这是什么？
What's this?
这是我的童年
It's my childhood
我们走吧
Let's go
好吧，挑你的家伙吧
All right, pick your poison
我喜欢左轮手枪，他们从不卡壳
I like a revolver They never jam
这是“准确性和停止力”
This is accuracy and stopping power
这是“战术”
This is tactical
他一直在等今晚
He waited for this night
在等我
He's waited for me
我一直在等他
I've waited for him
来吧，迈克尔
Come on, Michael
艾莉森，睁大你的眼睛
Allyson, keep your eyes open
他在外面的某个地方
He is out there somewhere
嫌疑犯在圣公园11号在附近
Suspect reported on 11th, near Saint Park
收到，总台
Copy that, Dispatch
我眼神很好
I got eyes
看！是他！
Look! It's him!
我们开始吧
Here we go
振作起来
Brace yourselves
不要打他！
Don't hit him!
小心！迈克尔！
Watch out! Michael!
不要开枪打他
Don't shoot him
医生，回到车里去 - 不！
Doctor, get back in the car - No!
你杀了他。他死了
You killed him. He's dead
退后 - 不
Stand back  -No
我还是要轰掉这个混蛋的脑袋
I'm still gonna blow this motherfucker's brains out
走开，离开我的病人
Get away Leave my patient alone
离开那个身体，退后
Get away from the body. Stand back
我不会再说了，离嫌疑犯身体远一点
I'm not gonna say it again Step away from the suspect
步骤一
Step a
干!
Fuck
救命！救命！
Help! Help!
救命！
Help!
so,就是这个feel
So this is what it feels like
救命！
Help!
给我的病人腾出地方 - 不！
Make room for my patient - No!
不
No
不！
No!
那些人因为你看到的
These people want to kill this man
那些罪行想杀了这个人
for the crimes you observed
这是最重要的机会
The most important opportunity
来理解邪恶的思想，你瞧
to understand the mind of evil, you see
所以，当他醒来时，我们就准备好了
So, when he awakes, we'll be ready
准备好什么？
Ready for what?
重聚
The reunion
迈克尔对劳丽・斯特罗德的追求
Michael's pursuit of Laurie Strode
可能是他活着的原因
could be what keeps him alive
我怀疑掠食者的概念
I would suspect the notion of being a predator
或者害怕成为猎物让他们俩都活着
or the fear of becoming prey keeps both of them alive
你想要一份越南三明治吗？
You want a banh mi sandwich?
发现更多的东西失去兴趣了
in discovering anything further
这就是我们在这里的原因
Well, that's why we're here
迈克尔是我一生的痴迷
Michael has been my life's obsession
我检查了他的每一份案卷
I've examined every single case file written on him
我是卢米斯博士生前的学生
I was a student of Dr. Loomis before he passed away
然后我亲自游说把伊利诺伊大学
And then I lobbied the University of Illinois
分配给迈克尔
to be assigned to Michael myself
有进展吗？
Any progress?
50多名临床精神病医生看过他，
Well, he's been seen by over 50 clinical psychiatrists,
每个人都有不同的观点
and with each, many different opinions
卢米斯博士是唯一一个在野外见到他的人
Dr. Loomis was the only one to see him in the wild
他断定他是纯粹的邪恶
And he concluded he was nothing more than pure evil
我们的病人在这有新鲜空气、阳光，
Our patients get fresh air, sunshine,
景观、适当的锻炼、健康的饮食
a view, proper exercise, healthy diet
看到他被转移到
It pains me to see him transferred
不太理想的疗养院让我很痛苦
to that less-than-desirable facility
他在那儿
And there he is
他能说话
He can speak
他只是选择不讲
He just chooses not to
如果可能的话，我想站得离他更近点
I'd love to stand closer to him, if I may
了解他的意识，或者他缺乏的意识
Get a sense of his awareness, or lack of awareness
哦，别犯错误啊，他很警觉
Oh, make no mistake, he's aware
当你刚来时，他正看着你
He was watching you as you arrived
也许你该把你左脚的鞋带系上
Perhaps you'd like to tie your left shoelace?
托沃利先生，拿着伞的那位
Mr. Tovoli here, the gentleman with the umbrella,
对这种事情很固执
has a fixation for such things
不要低估任何人
Underestimate no one
当然当然
Of course
现在走上黄线
And now step up to the yellow line
别再往前了
And no further
在任何情况下都不要越界
Do not cross the line under any circumstances
迈克尔
Michael
我这有几个人想见见你
I've got some people who'd like to meet you
你好，迈克尔
Hello, Michael
我叫亚伦・科瑞
My name is Aaron Korey
我跟踪你的案子已经好几年了
I've been following your case for years
仍然对你知之甚少
and still know very little about you
我想了解更多
I'd like to know more
关于那晚
About that night
关于那些牵扯其中的人
About those involved
迈克尔，你有想过他们吗？
Do you ever think about them, Michael?
对他们的命运感到内疚吗？
Feel guilt about their fate?
我从朋友那里借了些东西
I borrowed something from a friend
从总检察长办公室，迈克尔
at the attorney general's office, Michael
什么？那是什么？
A what? What is that?
一份越南三明治 - 什么是
A banh mi sandwich - What's a
那是什么？我甚至不知道那是什么
Wh-What is that? I don't even know what that is
弗朗西斯，我就喜欢你这一点，你很容易看透
I love that about you, Francis You're so predictable
你就是个每天吃PB&J（花生果酱）三明治的人
You're like a PB and J every day kind of guy
哦，我们走了
Oh, here we go
不，一份越南三明治
No, a banh mi sandwich
banh mi基本上就是
Banh mi is essentially just
越南语版本的法国面包
the Vietnamese version of a French baguette
这个词实际上是指
Mm-hmm And the term actually refers
面包而不是面包中里的东西
to the bread and not so much the contents therein
但是你的搭档，
Mm But your partner,
世界上最伟大的伙伴
the greatest partner in the world Oh
和越南人在餐馆里商量
made an arrangement with the Vietnamese folks
嗯
at the restaurant Mm
让他们给你做了私家
and had them make you your very own
花生酱果酱越式三明治
peanut butter and jelly banh mi sandwich
听起来很恶心
That sounds disgusting
我不会去尝试的，我自己带了食物
I'm not gonna try that I brought my own food
我对我的食物很满意，- 你带来了什么？
I'm very happy with my - What did you bring?
你想看看我带来了什么？
You want to see what I brought?
是的，我真想看看你带来了什么
Yeah, I do want to see what you brought
你为什么不看看这个？
Why don't you look at this?
看看那个哦
Look at that Oh
新鲜布朗尼 - 好的
Fresh brownie -Okay
巧克力是家里做的布朗尼是我自己做的
Chocolaty homemade brownie I made that myself
那是――那是，像，一个五岁小孩吃的
That's-that's, like, what a five-year-old would eat
如果他们能自己做午餐
if they could make their own lunch
我和迈克尔一起多年，
I worked with Michael for years,
但是我从未见过他在不受控制的环境中
but I've never seen him in an uncontrolled environment
我从没听过他说话，你瞧
I've never heard him speak, you see
尽管我鼓励他，他仍然反应迟钝
In spite of my encouragements, he remains unresponsive
但是今晚，有这么多的可能性
But tonight, so many possibilities exist
他跟我说过话
He spoke to me
他跟你说过话？ - 是
He spoke to you?  - Yeah
嗯，呃，当他谋杀我的朋友时，
Um, uh, when he murdered my friend,
他看见了我，然后他和我说话
he saw me, and-and he spoke to me
他说了什么？
What did he say?
一个词 - 什么？
One word  - What?
放了我，我会告诉你他说了什么
Let me go, and I will tell you what he said
你必须告诉我我必须知道，你必须告诉我
You must tell me I must know. You must tell me
放开我，我会告诉你他说了什么
Let me go, and I'll tell you what he said
停车，我会告诉你他说了什么
Just stop the car, and I'll tell you what he said
那是什么？
What is that?
这很奇怪，对吧？
That's weird, right?
那是霍金斯吗？
Is that Hawkins?
我不知道
I don't know
这个词是什么？
What was the word?
是姐姐的名字吗？
Was it the sister's name?
朱迪思？
Judith?
这个词是什么？他妈的
What was the word? Fuck
迈克尔
Michael
606 to 601
霍金斯
Hawkins
回复无线，疲劳的家伙
Answer the fucking radio, burnout
霍金斯？
Hawkins?
606, 601
霍金斯，请回答
Hawkins, please respond
霍金斯
Hawkins
我们去看看好吗
Let's go check it out All right
说点啥吧
Say something
你能看见他吗？
Can you see him?
霍金斯，请回答
Hawkins, please respond
我们去看看
Let's go and check it out
好
All right
呼叫总台，这里有个男性挂了
Dispatch, be advised, we got a man down
代码10 - 7
He's ten-seven
没有601的迹象
No sign of 601
凯伦，灯
Karen, the lights
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我以为你说我们在这里更安全
I thought you said we were safer here
当我谈到那天晚上的时候，你从来不想听
You never wanted to listen when I spoke of that night
这就是为什么
And this is why
我已经为此做了很长时间的准备
I've been preparing for this for a long time
你想让他过来
You want him to come here
我很抱歉，凯伦，我很抱歉，宝贝
I'm so sorry, Karen I'm so sorry, baby
有消息吗？
Any word?
嘿，有关于艾莉森的消息吗？
Hey, any word on Allyson?
嘿
Hey
各位
Guys
什么...？
Wha...?
雷！
Ray!
凯伦！
Karen!
雷在哪里？
Where's Ray?
迈克尔来了。去地下室
Michael's here. Get downstairs
快去，宝贝，快去！
Go, baby, go!
妈妈！
Mom!
我这样抚养你是错误的，
I was wrong to raise you the way I did,
但至少我能保护你
but at least I can protect you
你不会有事的
Nothing will happen to you
我知道你以为这是我的笼子
I know you thought this was my cage
我很害怕
I'm scared
我必须完成这个
I have to finish this
妈妈
Mom
我爱你
I love you
我爱你，宝贝
I love you, baby
你感觉到了吧，是吧，迈克尔？
You feel it, don't you, Michael?
你感觉到面具了吗
You feel the mask
费加罗。费加罗！
Figaro. Figaro!
说话，迈克尔
Say something, Michael
说话啊
Say something
你能感觉到，不是吗？
You can feel it, can't you?
这是你身体的一部分啊，迈克尔
It's a part of you, Michael
这是你的一部分
It's a part of you
说话
Say something
说点什么，迈克尔
Say something, Michael
说话啊！
Say something!
我们要找什么？
What is it we're after?
好吧，
Okay, well,
目睹了那畜生被关起来的样子
having witnessed the animal in its captive state
但没有引起他任何反应，
and failed to provoke any sort of response,
我们现在追踪它的对应部分
we now track down its counterpart
会不会是一个怪物创造了另一个怪物？
Could it be that one monster has created another?
尽管将他们分开的铁锁和铁丝网
And although the iron bars and barbed wire
既坚固又锋利，
that separate them are both strong and sharp,
形而上学的界限模糊且细微
the metaphysical lines are blurred and slight
两者都孤立存在，被自己的恐惧所束缚
Both exist in isolation, fettered by their own fear
还有彼此的仇恨
-是这了
这里？
Here?
难道让这个恐怖的家伙
Could it be that the only hope
恢复的唯一希望
of rehabilitation Spooky
是通过对抗么？
is through confrontation?
谢绝来访
Access has been denied
私人财产。不准擅自闯入。
Private property. No trespassing.
你可能需要这个
You might need this
Dana，记者采访不用富兰克林爷爷的
Dana, journalists don't pay for their interviews
笑一个
Smile
我们在监控里
We're on camera
是
Yes
你好。嗯，我们在找劳丽・斯特罗德
Hello. Um, we're looking for Laurie Strode
我们，呃，嗯
We're, uh, um
我们正在制作播客，呃
we're-we're making a podcast, and, uh
我们是调查记者
We're investigative journalists
如果你有时间，我们已经走了很长的路
If you have a moment, we've traveled a very long way
3000富兰克林爷爷怎么样？
How does $3,000 sound?
你好
Hello
我们可以进来吗？
May we come in?
坐下来谈谈？
And-and sit down and talk?
因此
So
亚伦和我做了几个
Aaron and I have made several
获奖的公共广播节目
award-winning public radio exposés
我们的最后一个项目对二十年前
Our last project shed new light
的一起谋杀案有了新的发现
on a murder case from 20 years ago
我们喜欢用不偏不倚的眼光重新审视事件
We like to reexamine incidents with an unbiased lens
我相信从您经历
I believe there's a lot to learn
的恐怖中有很多东西值得了解
from the horrors you experienced
没什么可了解的
There's nothing to learn
根本没有新的见解
There are no new insights
或者新发现
or discoveries
那么，他是真的吗？
So, is he real?
谁？
Who?
夜魔
The Boogeyman
我看到你引用的
I read you quoted
你不相信妖怪？
You don't believe in the Boogeyman?
我相信迈克尔・迈尔斯，是疯狂的连环杀手，但是
I believe in Michael Myers, deranged serial killer, but
夜魔，不，我不信
the Boogeyman, no
哦，你应该信
Well, you should
好吧
Okay
迈克尔・迈尔斯是只是一个人
Michael Myers is a human being
他六岁时杀了他妹妹
who killed his sister when he was six years old
然后他来追杀你
Then he came after you
我们只是想知道为什么
We just want to know why
我们想要一瞥他的内心
We want a glimpse inside his mind
这就是为什么你的故事如此重要
That's why your story is so important
我的故事？
My story?
两次失败的婚姻
Two failed marriages
与你女儿和外孙女的关系很糟糕
Rocky relationship with your daughter and granddaughter
迈克尔・迈尔斯杀了五个人
Michael Myers murdered five people
他是一个我们需要了解的人？
And he's a human being we need to understand?
我两次离婚
I'm twice divorced
我是个废人
And I'm a basket case
他们要转移他
They're transferring him
明天7 : 00
Tomorrow, 7:00
他会――他会一直被关着直到他死
He'll-he'll be locked away until the end of his days
对，就该这么干
That's the idea
让我们谈谈有关部门过来
Let's talk about when the state came
带走了你的女儿
to take your daughter away
她才12岁
She was 12 years old
他们说你是个不称职的母亲
They said you were an unfit mother
你多久后才重新获得监护权？
How long until you regained custody?
我没有监护权
I didn't
但是你已经知道了
But you already knew that
劳丽，我们看见他了
Laurie, we saw him
我们见过迈克尔
We met with Michael
我给他看了面具
I showed him the mask
但什么都没发生
There was nothing
没有回应。什么都没发生
No response. Nothing
他不会和任何人说话
He won't talk to anyone
从来没有，但是
Never has, but
我想他可能会和你说话
I think he might speak with you
那么，你为什么不和他坐下来
So, why don't you sit down with him
说出所有你想说的话
and say all the things you must be longing to say
跟我们走，
Come with us,
让我们帮你解脱
and let us help you free yourself
请
Please
时间到了
Time's up
给钱吧
I'll accept my payment
出去
Get out
你想在我的水槽下面拉屎？
You want to shit under my sink?
我会杀了你和你全家
I will murder you and your whole family
我把棉花糖换成了花生酱
I switched from marshmallow fluff to peanut butter
看看那些小杂种吃不吃
See if those little bastards eat that
那应该会杀了他们
That ought to kill them
我重新安排了我最后一个会议的时间，这样我今晚就可以了
I rescheduled my last session, so I can make it tonight
妈妈，你真的没必要这么做
You really didn't have to do that, Mom
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal
你进入了国家荣誉协会
You made it into the National Honor Society
是的，这是件大事
Yeah That is a very big deal
我只是刚刚把我的手工做到了最上面一层
I just made it to the top of my shop class,
做鸟窝，呃，用柚木做棋盘
making birdhouses and, uh, a checkerboard made of teak
我们很高兴见到卡梅伦
We're excited to meet Cameron
然而，他们全家都有名声
That whole family, though, they had a reputation
-雷，别这样
-Ray, come on
-这是一个相关因素
-It's a relevant factor
你还记得有一次朗尼
Do you remember the one time Lonnie
在警察脸上打了一拳？
punched that cop in the face?
-雷
-Ray
哦！妈了个
Oh! Mother
哦，靠！
Oh, man!
派隙际腔ㄉ酱
I got peanut butter on my penis
噫~我亲爹啊
Ew, Dad
报应不爽啊
Instant karma
卡梅伦是个好人，他不是你说的那样的人
Cameron is a good guy He's nothing like that
你今晚见到他时就知道了
You're gonna see when you meet him tonight
对，他们都是好人，直到他们把你肚子搞大
They're all nice guys until they get you pregnant,
然后你就得开他们的皮卡，
and then you gotta drive in their pickup trucks,
跟他们打炮，有一堆孩子
and you clean their guns, and you got children,
接着打炮，然后跟他们嗑嗨了
and you clean guns, and you like to get high with them,
然后你就肥了
and then y'all get fat
嘿，亲爹啊？
Hey, Dad?
怎么？
What?
我得把手上的花生酱弄干净
I gotta clean this peanut butter off my hand
你说你邀请老奶，你请了么
Did you invite Grandmother like you said you would?
今晚的事，你说你会
About tonight You said that you'd
哦
Oh
对。我请了
Right. I did
-是吗？
-You did?
我昨天和她谈过了
I talked to her yesterday
她不能来了，亲爱的。对不起
She's not gonna be able to come, honey. I'm sorry
真的吗？
Really?
是
Yeah
宝贝，她有陌生环境恐惧症
Baby, she's agoraphobic
她需要认知行为治疗
She needs cognitive behavioral therapy,
所以不要把这个当成针对你个人的
so don't take it personally
那是维基。我得走了
That's Vicky. I gotta go
嘿，我爱你
Hey, I love you
祝你愉快
Have a good day
再见，老爹，爱你哦
Bye, Dad. Love you Okay
所以，我妈是个骗子
So, my mom's a liar
怎么了？
What happened?
她说她今晚邀请了
She said that she invited
我祖母，但她没有
my grandmother tonight, but she didn't
我的意思是，她甚至没有联系过她
I mean, she never even contacted her
你怎么知道的？因为我自己打电话给她了
How do you know? Because I called her myself
-这也太扯了 -是啊
-That's bullshit -Yeah
老兄，你妈怎么了？她为什么要那么说？
Dude, what's your mom's deal? Why would she say that?
我不知道。她就是想让我离她远点
I don't know. She just tries to keep me away from her
我家里的每个人，就好像
Everyone in my family, like,
一年中的这个时候都变成了个疯子
turns into a total nutcase this time of year
如果我是你们，我也不会庆祝
If I were you guys, I wouldn't celebrate, either
我就放一棵圣诞树就行了
I would just put up a Christmas tree instead
跳过所有令人毛骨悚然的狗屎万圣节，对吧？
Just skip all over the creepy Halloween shit, right?
你老奶说过这些么？
Does your grandma ever talk about it?
是的，这几乎是她说的的全部
Yeah, it's pretty much all she talks about
它定义了她的生活
It defines her life
从那以后，她精神上受打击很大
She's been traumatized ever since
是不是她哥哥，
Wasn't it her brother who, like,
冷血谋杀了所有这些青少年？
cold-blooded murdilated all those teenagers?
不
No
我觉得这只是一些人瞎编的
That's just a bit that some people made up
为了让他们自己觉得好受
to make them feel better, I think
我的意思是，自己的一群朋友被
I mean, that is scary to have a bunch of your friends
随便一个疯子杀掉这件事太可怕了
get butchered by some random crazy person
是吗？但是，从大方面考虑，
Is it, though? Because, all things considered,
今天发生了很多更糟糕的事情
there's a lot worse stuff that's happening today
我是说，有几个人被人拿到砍死了
And, like, I mean, what, a couple people getting killed
并不是什么大不了的事
by one guy with a knife is not that big of a deal
伙计，她的老奶差点被杀了唉
Dude, her grandmother was almost fucking murdered
她逃掉了，他们抓住了他，
And she escaped, and they caught him,
现在他被监禁了
and now he's incarcerated
我就是说说的，比如，按照今天的标准
I-I'm just saying, like, by today's standards
你TMD闭嘴吧，戴夫
Just shut the fuck up, Dave
闭肛
Shut up
哦，对不起，呵~闭嘴，戴夫
Oh, I'm sorry Yeah, shut up, Dave
嘿，如果我把
Hey, is it cool with you guys
其中一个南瓜头给炸了，你们没意见吧？
if I explode one of these pumpkin heads?
没意见。是啊，去吧
Yeah. Yeah Go for it
哦，他是认真的么？
Oh, he's serious?
他是认真的，哦，天哪，他真要把那给炸了
He's serious Oh, God, he's really blowing it up
我知道他就是个T妈的傻
I know He's such a fucking moron
哦，上帝。哦，上帝 - 哦，天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God  - Oh,Jesus
闪，快闪，闪了
Go, go, go, go, go
万圣节快乐！
Happy Halloween!
啊！
Ah!
卡梅伦
Cameron
吓到你了吧，不错哦
I got you That was a good one
是的，很不错
Yes, that was very good
嘿，明晚的东西都准备齐了么
Hey, do you have everything
明晚晚上的礼服之类的
for your costume tomorrow night?
邦妮和克莱德必须合二为一，毕竟嗯
Bonnie and Clyde must roll as one, after all Um
不，我是说，今晚我更专注
no, I mean, I-I'm more focused on tonight
今晚？
Tonight?
你说你父母很守旧的时候
I-I thought you were joking when you said
我还以为你在开玩笑
your parents were old-fashioned
乖一点，好吗？- 行
Be nice, okay? - Okay
会很好玩的
It'll be fun
今晚我很兴奋 - 我需要冷静下来
I'm excited for tonight - I need to calm down
今晚我很兴奋，行吗？- 行
I'm excited for tonight, okay?  -Okay
哦，啊，哦
Ooh
呃。你们俩简直太恶心了，知道么
Ugh. You guys are just barf, you know
你俩只是两个恶心的矮胖子，
You're just you're two yucky dumpsters,
我也想来一下。过来。么啊！- 别
and I want to go diving. Come here. Mwah! - No
兄弟，兄弟 - 就这，就这，行吧？
Dude, dude - Right here, right here, right?
么么么啊 - 伙计，你你
Oh. Mwah, mwah - Dude, you-you got
你的烂嘴弄了我
your little chapped-lip crusties
一身口水，伙计，所以真谢谢你
all over me, man, so thanks
我知道，不用谢我
I know. And you're welcome
太恶心了- 这唇是我身体专门给
It's gross  - It's a little part of me for you
你余生准备的
For the rest of your day
怎么样？那么
All right? So, do you have
明天你的服装准备好了吗？
everything ready for your costume tomorrow?
嗯...关于那个 - 怎么了？
Um... about that - What?
你们是认真的么？
Are we seriously not?
你说过我们要一起跳万圣节舞的
You said we were gonna do this whole Halloween dance together
现在你们把我踢了
Now-now you just you ditch me
我的意思是，你只是你――你不带这么
I mean, you just you-you can't walk
欺负人的 - 好吧，好吧
all over town breaking hearts - Okay, okay, okay
嘿，听着，听着  - 怎么样？
Hey, listen, listen - All right?
真爱啊 - 好吧，情侣们，一会再闹好么
Love. Truly - Okay lovebirds, later
现在让我们把书翻到
Now let's open our books to
弗兰克尔的解释
Frankl's interpretation
他说，命运选择了不同的道路
He said, Fate took a different course
我理解这个世界上一个一无所有的人
I understand how someone who has nothing left in this world
可能仍然知道幸福。
may still know bliss.
他传达的信息给人以希望
His message is totally hopeful
即使在最恶劣的条件下，
Even in the most disparaging of conditions,
生活也可以找到它的意义
life can find its meaning,
相反，一个人的痛苦也是如此
and conversely, so can one's suffering
i
I
这钱我不能要
can't accept this
用它来满足你内心的愿望
Use it for whatever your heart desires
那我就把它存起来上大学
I'll save it for college, then
去他妈的大学
Fuck college
去什么地方，去墨西哥
Go somewhere. Go to Mexico
你能想象吗？
Could you imagine?
是的，我可以
Yeah, I can
听着，别担心你妈妈
Look, don't worry about your mom
她会发疯的
She will freak
但是她会克服的
But she'll get over it
你为什么不能克服？
Why can't you?
夜魔？
The Boogeyman?
所有这些躲躲藏藏，所有这些准备，
All this hiding, all this preparation,
其实没有意义
it was for nothing
我的意思是，这些弄得比你的家庭更重要
I mean, it took priority over your family
这让你失去了家人
It cost you your family
如果我抚养你母亲的方式意味着她恨我
If the way I raised your mother means that she hates me
但是她已经对这个
but that she's prepared
恐怖的世界做好了准备，那么
for the horrors of this world, then
我可以忍受
I can live with that
跟迈克尔说再见，然后忘掉这些
Say good-bye to Michael, and get over it
我走了，拜
Good-bye
塞缪尔・卢米斯博士，
Dr. Samuel Loomis,
1979年1月22日
January 22, 1979
你想就以下问题发表声明吗
Do you wish to give a statement regarding
关于你的前病人迈克尔・迈尔斯？
your former patient, Michael Myers?
我的建议是终结
My suggestion is termination
死亡是迈克尔唯一的解决办法
Death is the only solution for Michael
A2201。迈克尔・迈尔斯
A2201. Myers, Michael
脚趾排成一行。保持一条线。让魔鬼活着
Toes in line. Keep a line .There's nothing
你是讨不到好的。 - 手举起来
to be gained from keeping evil alive  - Hands up!
举起手来！站起来！
Hands up! Stand up!
A22
一针硫喷妥钠
A shot of sodium thiopental
会使他失去知觉
would render him unconscious
A22我会和他在一起以确保
A22 I'll be with him to make sure
他的生命消失
his life is extinguished
我的耳朵贴在他的胸口，亲子听
My ear on his chest to hear for myself
他的身体器官不再起作用
that his vitals no longer function
并立即焚烧尸体
and immediately incinerate the body
它必须得死
It needs to die
它必须死！
It needs to die!
继续前进。我们走吧
Keep moving. Let's go
别担心，迈克尔
Don't worry, Michael
我会在你身边
I'll be by your side
迈克尔・迈尔斯仍然是我的病人
Michael Myers is still my patient
直到他被别人照顾
until he's in somebody else's care,
所以我一直坚持到最后
so I'm seeing my duty through till the end
好了，出发
All right, move out
把我的DNA寄给一个陌生人
send my DNA away to a stranger
为什么不呢？你可以发现一些非常有趣的事情
Why not? You can find out some pretty interesting things
我不就发现我是切诺基混血么
Don't I found out that I'm part Cherokee
我猜我爸爸大概有百分之七的切诺基血统
I guess my dad's, like, seven percent Cherokee
我认识朗尼，我和他一起上过高中
I know Lonnie I went to high school with him
他曾经卖给我迷幻药 - 老爹
He used to sell me peyote  - Dad
每个人都认识朗尼 -是的。-爸爸
Everyone knows Lonnie - Yeah. - Dad
对不起，好吧。嗯
I'm sorry All right. Um
这是一个信息量过大的分享
this is a massive overshare
对我们的新朋友来说 - 不，他确实做过
for our new friend - No, he did
我和他爸爸一起自我探索了很多东西
I learned a lot about myself with his dad
我和他爸爸在树林里玩的很嗨 - 老爹
Tripped balls out in the woods, me and his dad  -Dad
孩子，雷・很嗨。-爸爸！
Boy, Ray Tripping balls. - Dad!
不，真的，继续说
No, really, keep talking
所以，你们有明天的大计划
So, you guys have big plans for tomorrow
在高中？你们打算怎么搞？
at the high school? What are you doing?
是跳舞还是什么？是的，这是万圣节
Is it a dance or something? Yeah, it's a Halloween
服装？万圣节舞会。是
Costumes? Halloween dance. Yep
嗯！化装舞会
Mmm! Costume party
你打算做什么？
What are you going as?
呃，嗯，我不知道是否允许我说
Uh, well, I don't know if I'm allowed to say
请说吧，哦，来吧
Please say Oh, come on
来吧，我可以...？行
Come on I can...? Okay
嗯，那个我们就打扮成邦妮和克莱德
Uh, so we're going as Bonnie and Clyde
哦，这是个好主意
Oh, that's a great idea Yeah
除了 - 哦
Except - Oh!
哦。不
Oh. No Ooh
好吧，那么只有邦妮和克莱德
Okay, so just Bonnie and Clyde
就这样。邦妮和克莱德
That's it. Bonnie and Clyde
邦妮和克莱德搞一起
Bonnie and Clyde with a twist
经典耶！
Classic Yeah!
是啊！-我喜欢这个不错
Yeah! - I love that Nice
这太有趣了，你会看到的
That's so fun You'll see
你知道它是怎么结束的，对吧？
You know how it ended, right?
他们的故事结束得有点不错。有希望地
Their story ended a little Yes. Hopefully
是的，子弹和流血
Yes, with the bullets and the bleeding
是的，你有一辆老爷车
Yeah You have a jalopy
到处都是联邦探员的子弹孔？
filled with bullet holes from the G-men?
我希望我们有一个
I wish we had one of those
它在劳克林，就像我知道的A型车一样
It was in Laughlin, like a Model A I know
你和祖母谈过了吗？
Did you talk to Grandmother?
是
Yeah
她说她要来么？
She said she was gonna come
她来到我的办公室，我们谈得很愉快
She came to my office We had a nice talk
是吗？真的吗？
Did you? Really?
这是第一次很好
That's a first It was nice
哦，你知道她在哪里吗？
Oh Do you know where she is, then?
对不起。我很抱歉。我...哦
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I That part... Oh
好时机，妈妈。嗨，我
Great timing, Mom. Hi Uh, I
你成功了，我来迟了。对不起
You made it It ran late. I'm sorry
嗨。我很高兴你来嗨，妈妈。-嗨，劳丽
Hi. I'm so happy you came Hi, Mom. - Hi, Laurie
嗨。嗨。我，呃嗨
Hi. Hi. I'm, uh Hi
我是他外婆
I'm the grandmother
很高兴认识你，我是卡梅伦・埃兰
Nice to meet you I'm Cameron Elam
我们在这里庆祝我们的女儿
And we're here celebrating our daughter
因为她 - 是的，我知道
because of her - Yes, I know
怎么样了？
How did it go?
不错，你穿上很好看
Yes. It looks good on you
你知道，我也是荣誉协会的成员
You know, I was in the Honor Society, too
那很好，妈妈，你为什么不坐下来？
That's good 。Why don't you sit down, Mom?
不，我很好 - 来吧，坐吧
No, I'm good  - Yeah, have a seat
或者我们可以去散步，如果你愿意的话
Or we could go for a walk, if you'd like
真的吗？进展顺利吗？是吗？是
Really? Did it go great? Yeah? Yeah
真的去了，嗯
It went really it went, um
嘿，妈妈？那是我的
Hey, Mom? That's mine
我以为你戒酒了
I thought you quit drinking Mmm
妈妈，你在做什么？这是什么？
Mom, what are you doing? What is this?
你知道，这正是我们不联系的原因
You know, this is exactly why we don't reach out
妈妈
Mom
对不起。我会坐下
I'm sorry. I will sit down
行
Okay
我们为什么不按下复位按钮呢？
Why don't we press the reset button?
我们何不从头开始，好吗？
Why don't we just start over, okay?
嗯
Mm-hmm
好吧，妈妈
All right, Mom
对不起 - 妈妈
Sorry  - Mom
别这样了
Please stop this
对不起
Sorry
我看见他了
I saw him
形状
The Shape
妈妈  - 我想杀了他
Mom  - I wanted to kill him
好了，够了，劳丽
Okay, that's enough, Laurie
劳丽，够了， - 我不知道该怎么办
Laurie, that's enough  - I didn't know what to do
够了，劳丽 - 好了
That's enough, Laurie-  Okay
我想这可能对你来说承受的太多了，是吧？
I think maybe this is a little bit too much for you, huh?
我们出去走走吧，好吗？
Why don't we go for a walk, all right?
你说过你会尝试
You said you were gonna try
把过去抛在身后，劳丽
to put the past behind you Laurie
好吗？你会尝试这样做吗？
Okay? Are you gonna try to do that?
这就是你说你想做的
That's what you said you wanted to do
我不能
I can't
妈妈，看着我
Mom, look at me
看着我
Look at me
我应该 -我们 呃
I Should  - we, uh
我真的不想说我告诉过你的，但是
really hate to say I told you so, but
我很高兴你能看到这一点
I'm glad you got to see that
我从没告诉过你我是如何度过童年的
I never told you how I spent my childhood
找到你了
Gotcha
我八岁时学会了如何开枪
I learned how to shoot a gun when I was eight
我学会了如何战斗
I learned how to fight
我做了关于地下室的噩梦
I had nightmares about the basement
社会保障机构在我12岁的时候把我带走
Social Services came when I was
我花了一辈子的时间试图摆脱疑神疑鬼
I've spent my entire life trying to get over the paranoia
以及她投射在我身上的神经过敏
and neuroses that she has projected on me
是的，他有点提醒我
Yeah, he kind of reminds me
加里・霍格博姆的
of, uh, Gary Hogeboom
是啊，四分卫的事情都搞砸了
Yeah, that quarterback thing is all messed up
还不错，对吧？
Good times, right?
她自己会怎么处理？
What is she gonna do with herself?
我知道的，救她不是你的工作
I know It's not your job to save her
她会没事的
She'll be all right
收不到台啊
I can't get reception
自从天线在洗车场被
on this thing ever since the antenna
弄弯之后就收不到
was bent at the car wash
为什么我们要再次出来？
Why do we have to come out again?
我们总是这样做
We do this all the time
什么？你不喜欢吗？
What? You don't you don't enjoy it?
我喜欢在森林里
I-I like being out in the woods and
不，我喜欢，但是我错过了舞蹈课
No, I enjoy it, but I'm missing dance class for this
有时我宁愿这样做也不愿打猎
And sometimes I would rather do that than hunting
我的意思是，舞蹈课对你来说重要吗？
I mean, is-is-is dance class that important to you?
是的，确实重要 - 你需要更多的时间
Yeah, it is  -You need some more time
在森林里打猎和钓鱼 -不
in the woods to go hunting and fishing  - No
周末，我可以和你一起，爸爸
On weekends, I'll do it with you, Dad
比如，我真的很喜欢和你在一起，
Like, I really love spending time with you,
但是现在跳舞是我的事，你懂的，而且
but right now dancing is my thing, you know, and
我真的很用心，我的意思是，我
it really hits me in the heart I mean, I
爸爸，小心！哦！
Dad, look out! Oh!
霍斯，你到底怎么了？
What the hell happened to you, Hoss?
哦，妈的
Oh, shit
爸爸，看
Dad, look
小陆，你留在这里
Lumpy, you stay here
我过去看看有没有人受伤
I'm gonna make sure no one's hurt
你打电话报警，可以么？
You call the police Okay
爸爸，请小心
Dad, be careful, please
嘿，你们没事吧？
Hey, you fellas okay?
你没事吧？
You all right?
911. What is the emergency?
是的。嗯，发生了一起事故
Yes. Um, th-there's been an accident
呃，有一辆公共汽车
Uh, there's a bus
人们在路上跑来跑去
People running around in the road
我爸爸过去看了，我――我不知道
My dad went to look I-I don't know
好吧。继续
Okay. Hold on
我去看看
I'll go check
爸爸？
Dad?
快跑
Run
在这里等着
Wait here
我~我去找我爸爸
I-I'll go get my dad
不
N-No
快跑！
Run!
爸爸！
Dad!
Daddy!
不要开枪。啊！
Don't shoot. Aah!
哦，操！操！
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
乘坐这趟火车不需要信用卡。
Don't need a credit card to ride this train.
哟，霍克，听着，球松了，那是哪里
Yo, Hawk, listen, the ball come down loose, that's where
你会惹上麻烦的，-  嘿，霍金斯，你要
you're gonna mess up at - Yo, Hawkins, would you like
草莓汁还是蓝覆盆子汁？
a strawberry slushie or a blue raspberry slushie?
你给我来杯咖啡就行了，可以么？
Can you just bring me a coffee, will you?
我一会给你钱
I'll get you back later
拉一把弹弓，它会一直打到中间
Pull a slingshot, it'll go straight down the middle
但是你永远也打不赢我的分数，
But you ain't never gonna beat my score,
所以你做什么都没关系
so it makes no difference what you do
再说一遍，你永远不会
Say that again You're never gonna
击败我的分数，所以你做什么都没关系
beat my score, so it doesn't make no difference what you do
分派到手台601
Dispatch to unit 601
马拉路上有状况，代码10-50
We have a 10-50 on Marla Road
收到，我现在就行动
Copy that, dispatch I'm on my way
各单位注意，各单位注意
Attention, all units
我们警员有情况，代码10-23
We got an officer that's 10-23
出来，迈克尔
Come out, Michael
妈妈
Mom
外婆？
Grandmother?
宝贝儿
Baby
妈妈
Mom
他来了。快
He's coming. Come on
嘘。快点。快，- 外婆在哪里？
Shh. Come on. Come on - Where's Grandmother?
我找不到你们了
I couldn't I couldn't find you guys
每个人都在哪里？没关系。没关系
Where is everybody? It's okay. It's okay
没事的，我被关在笼子里了
It's gonna be okay I'm locked in a cage
会没事的会没事的
It's gonna be okay It's gonna be okay
退后
Stay back
回来！回去，回去
Get back! Get back, get back
哦，上帝
Oh, God
退后
Stay back
妈妈？
Mom?
救救我们！
Help us!
我做不到
I can't do it
对不起。我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't do it
逮着你了
Gotcha
万圣节快乐，迈克尔
Happy Halloween, Michael
来吧，艾莉森！
Come on, Allyson!
加油，艾莉森！艾莉森，快走！
Come on, Allyson! Allyson, go!
艾莉森，加油！
Allyson, come on!
快走！
Go!
凯伦，加油，宝贝，加油！
Karen, come on, baby Come on!
哦，上帝！
Oh, God!
我抓住你了！
I got you!
艾莉森，快跑！
Allyson, run!
走吧！走吧！
Go! Go now!
来吧，踢他！
Come on, kick him!
艾莉森！艾莉森，走！走吧！
Allyson! Allyson, go! Go!
现在走！
Now go!
好吧。这不是笼子，宝贝
Okay. It's not a cage, baby
这是个陷阱
It's a trap
再见，迈克尔
Good-bye, Michael
哦，上帝，有人来了
Oh, God, someone's coming
有人来了
Someone's coming
抱着她，我抓住她了
Hold her I got her
我抓住她了。去吧！
I got her. Go!
去吧，宝贝，去！
Go, baby, go!
嘿！
Hey!
帮助我们
Help us
或者10-50，在二十号公路。我们会提供建议
and a possible 10-50 on Route 20. Will advise
警察局的
Sheriff's Department
可能代码10 - 98。结束。
Possible 10-98. Over
如果你需要帮助，让别人知道你
If you need assistance, let yourself be known
代码13
Signal 13
警官受伤
Officer down
我重复一遍:有警官受伤
I repeat: officer down
我需要现在马上增派支援
I need assistance Send backup right away
收到
Uh, roger that
10 - 1，警官受伤
Ten-one, officer down
发送到EMT和所有可用电台
Sending EMT and all available units
呼哦
Ooh
举起手来！
Show your hands!
我中枪了
I've been shot
好吧，和我在一起。支援马上就来
All right, stay with me Help's on the way
这里发生了什么？
What happened in here?
他逃跑了吗？
Did he escape?
谁？
Who?
谁逃跑了？
Did who escape?
我有个表弟在墓地工作
Well, I got a cousin works at a graveyard
离这里不远嗯
not too far from here Hmm
那边有将军，
They got war generals,
慈善家，披头士诗人
philanthropists, a beatnik poet
有穆迪沃特斯（蓝调歌手，芝加哥蓝调之父）
They got Muddy Waters
哦，还有伯尼・麦克了（电视人）
Oh, and they got Bernie Mac
人们从各地来表达敬意
People come from all over to pay respects
但这是哈登菲尔德镇
But this is Haddonfield,
这是我们唯一的名声
and this is our only claim to fame
也许你可以跟我说说
Maybe you can explain to me
朱迪思・迈尔斯有什么特别之处
what's so special about Judith Myers
当她坐着梳理头发时，没有意识到，
As she sat combing her hair, unaware,
她六岁的弟弟悄悄地进来了
her six-year-old brother crept in quietly
拿着菜刀
with a kitchen knife
然后，他开始切开她的头骨底部，
He then proceeded to slice the base of her skull,
刮她的脊髓
scraping her spinal cord
当她转身时，
When she turned,
她举起双手自卫，
raising her hands in self-defense,
他继续刺入
he continued stabbing
她的手掌神经和动脉
into the nerves and arteries of her palms
又扎了她胸骨三刀，
Three more stabs into her sternum,
穿透她的心
penetrating her heart
霍金斯
Hawkins
还在检查我们找到的病人的身份证
Still checking I.D.'s of the patients we recovered
找出谁是谁
to figure out who's who
基本上就靠
Almost all accounted for
在图书馆查看他们两人的电子邮件了
Two of them were checking their e-mails at a local library
刚刚发现其中三个人握着手，
Just found three of 'em holding hands,
在跳蚤市场追逐蝴蝶
chasing butterflies at a flea market off the 220
蝴蝶？
Butterflies?
仍然不知道到底发生了什么
Still no idea what really went down
瑞普・凡・温克尔先生有什么消息吗？
Any word from Mr. Rip van Winkle over here?
护士说他时好时坏
Nurses say he's been in and out,
失血过多
lost a lot of blood
不知怎的，挨了一枪
Somehow managed to fall on a bullet
我正尝试了解事情经过
I'm trying to get the whole story
因为我担心的是:
because here's my concern:
看看这个列表
Take a look at this list
他们中的大多数是未成年罪犯、精神病人
Most of 'em minor offenders, mental patients
一个突出的: A2201
One stuck out: A2201
那是迈克尔・迈尔斯
It's Michael Myers
保姆谋杀案，1978年
Babysitter Murders, 1978
40 years to this day
40年了到现在
迈克尔・迈尔斯和一群疯子
Michael Myers loose with a bunch of nutbags
万圣节晚上在哈顿菲尔德镇上闲逛？
in Haddonfield on Halloween night?
这下她妈的热闹了
We're gonna have a fucking circus on our hands
但是嘿
But hey
我们能该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
取消万圣节？
Cancel Halloween?
雷医生，请接二号线
Dr. Ray, please pick up line two
我需要马上去做第二件事
I need to go do a number two almost immediately
我能开车吗？来吧，上车。走吧
Can I drive? Come on, get in the car. Move it
有要在店里买的东西么？
Want anything from the shop?
不，不，谢谢
No. No, thank you
嗯
Hmm
洗手间在哪里？对不起？
Where's the loo? Excuse me?
洗手间
Bathroom
在那边，在后面
It's out that way, around the back
对不起。遗憾的
Excuse me. Sorry
有人在这里
Someone's in here
喂？
Hello?
什么...？
What the...?
帮我！
Help me!
啊！帮我！
Aah! Help me!
亚伦！亚伦！
Aaron! Aaron!
啊！放开我！
Aah! Get off me!
亚伦！停下！
Aaron! Stop!
帮我！
Help me!
迈克尔
Michael
亚伦！亚伦！
Aaron! Aaron!
黛娜！
Dana!
不！不，求你勒
No! No, please
黛娜！
D-Dana!
亚伦
Aaron
不！不
No! No
警方还没有确定
Police have not determined
这次事故的原因
a cause of this accident
当然，这一幕还是很有用的
Uh, this scene's still very active, of course
你可以看到我身后的警察录像带
You can see the police tape set up behind me
那辆囚车稳稳地停在沟里
That prison bus firmly down in that ditch
你也可以看到拖车，
You can see the tow truck, of course,
试图把那辆监狱巴士弄出来
that is trying to get that prison bus out
一个消息来源告诉我们那辆公共汽车
A source tells us that bus
正在运送当地州立医院的人员
was transporting personnel from a local state hospital
13 A-9
罗杰
Roger
雷？
Ray?
艾莉森？
Allyson?
艾莉森？有人在家吗？
Allyson? Is anyone home?
凯伦？嘘
Karen? Shh
什么？
What?
抓住了！-天啊
Gotcha! - Jesus
你死了
You're dead
你吓到我了！
You scared me!
你在我们家干什么？
What are you doing in our house?
你是说，我是怎么进你家的？
You mean, how did I get into your house?
凯伦，你没有安全系统
You have no security system, Karen
你的侧窗开得很大
Your side window was wide open
有时候我分不清
Sometimes I can't tell the difference
你的愚蠢和无知之间的区别
between your stupidity and your ignorance
嘿，劳丽，这是我的家，
Hey, Laurie, this is my home,
我可以照顾自己的家庭，好吗？
and I can take care of my own family, all right?
我知道柔术，我学过
I know jujitsu I have studied
公共汽车撞了雷
The bus crashed Ray
什么？- 听着，我有个计划
What? - Look, I have a plan
阿廖森在哪里？我们现在需要离开这里
Where's Allyson? We need to get out of here now
什么巴士坠毁了？
What bus crashed?
放下枪。放下 - 嘿，嘿。退后！
Put down that gun. Put down - Hey, hey. Back off!
放下枪，你在我的...放下枪！
Put down that gun. You're in my... Put down the gun!
妈妈，你需要治疗
Mom, you need help,
在你好之前，这个房子不欢迎你
and you are not welcome in this house until you get it
我试图保护你，让你做好准备
I have tried to protect you and prepare you
现在我们必须追捕他把他放倒
Now we have to hunt him down
是的，我正在为我的家人准备晚餐
Yeah, and I am trying to prepare dinner for my family
这个世界不是一个黑暗邪恶的地方
The world is not a dark and evil place
它充满了爱和理解，
It is full of love and understanding,
我不会让你的精神病狂言迷惑我
and I'm not letting your psychotic rants confuse me
或者说服我
or convince me otherwise
拿着枪！ - 不你得走了
Keep the gun - No! You need to go
出去！
Get out!
婊子养的
Son of a bitch
霍金斯
Hawkins
弗兰克！
Frank!
是吗？
Yeah?
看看这个
Look at this
这是国家发布的医院病号服
It's a hospital gown State-issued
打电话到史密斯森林
Get on the phone to Smith's Grove
确认匹不匹配
Confirm the match
你知道那天晚上我也在那里。你是知道的
You know I was there that night. You know
我在那里
I was there
我们有一个任务
We have one order of business
那是为了干掉这个玩意
That's to hunt this thing down
今晚我们害怕是有原因的
There's a reason we're supposed to be afraid of this night
不给糖就捣蛋！不给糖就捣蛋！
Trick or treat! Trick or treat!
我们去哪家
Which one should we go to?
他们都很恐怖
They're all spooky
我要选那个
I'm gonna pick that one
在街对面
over, um, across the street
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh
什么...？对不起，嘿。很抱歉
What the...? Sorry Hey. Sorry about that
黑猫和妖
Black cats and goblins
扫帚和鬼魂，
and broomsticks and ghosts,
女巫集会
Covens of witches with all of their hosts,
你可能认为他们吓到我了，
You may think they scare me,
你可能是对的
You're probably right,
万圣节之夜黑猫和妖
Black cats and goblins on Halloween night
求你了！
Please!
请让我们离开这里！他们从哪里来的？
Please let us out of here! Where did they come from?
你来自地狱
You are from the other side
你带着标志
You are the sign
不给糖就捣蛋！嘿，伙计们。呆在一起
Trick or treat! Hey, guys. Stay together
非常可怕
Very scary
米拉。米拉，不！不给糖就捣蛋！
Mila. Mila, no! Trick or treat
轮到你了
Wait your turn
给我点好吃的等等，等等，等等
give me something good to eat Wait, hang on, hang on
我听诊器没带，快点！
I don't have my stethoscope Come on!
我需要它。我去拿，我们要迟到了
I need it. I'm gonna get it We're going to be late
我马上回来，天啊！
I'll be right back Geez!
看。你不会相信的
Look. You're not gonna believe this
他们一直在我口袋里
They were in my pocket the whole time
丽贝卡给你地址了么？
Did Rebecca give you directions?
是的。她打过电话给我。
Yeah. She did call me
嘿，莎莉。你好吗？
Hey, Sally. How are you?
真的吗？
Really?
太可怕了
That's awful
好吧，我会锁门
Well, I'll keep my doors locked
谢谢你告诉我
Thanks for telling me
比利还在派对上
Billy's still out at a party
如果你听到其他消息，请告诉我
Let me know if you hear anything else
晚安，莎莉
Good night, Sally
不给糖就捣蛋！
Trick or treat!
邦妮和克莱德，你是少女杀手
Bonnie and Clyde, you are lady-killers
你们真的很漂亮
You guys are seriously beautiful
你真漂亮，给我一个微笑
You're seriously beautif Give me a smile
给我一个大大的微笑，抱紧她
Give me a big smile Just hold her tight
走起，用你的屁股
There we go. Do that Do that with your ass
好吧，所以，不，不
Okay, so, no, not
是维基，一秒钟。一秒钟
It's Vicky One second. One sec
好吧，你不需要，你不必拿着它
Okay, you don't you don't have to take it
嗨。哦，天哪，我希望你在这里
Hi. Oh, my gosh, I wish that you were here
这太有趣了
It is so much fun
上帝，我希望我在那里，我真他妈的很沮丧
God, I wish I was there I'm so fuckin' bummed
这就像，其实~如果你不知道
It's just, like, so much easier
你在和谁聊天的时候
to actually, like, talk to people when you have no idea
这样交谈就容易多了- 是的，伙计，我告诉过你很好玩的
who they are  - Yeah, dude, I told you you'd have fun
卡梅伦怎么样？他看起来很好吗
How's Cameron? Is he looking super fine
穿着我奶奶的裙子？
in my grandma's skirt?
他
He is
太性感了，有点过了
so sexy, it's a little too much to take
但是
But
你咋了？没什么，他太可爱了
Where'd you go? No, he's so sweet
我玩得很开心 - 你们最好
I'm having the best time  - You know, you guys
晚会结束后来我这
should just come over here when it's done
戴夫已经在路上了，他会带着，呃，
Dave's already on his way, and he's gonna bring the, uh,
你知道的，阿拉卡萨姆（大麻），你懂的
you know, the Alakazam, if you know what I mean
朱利安的父母今晚不会回来了
And Julian's parents aren't gonna be back
直到超级晚了
until, like, super late
好吧，好吧，这是一个学校之夜，
Okay, well, it is a school night,
所以我们不要嗨大了
so we're not gonna kazam too much
哦，拜托，这是一个学校之夜
Oh, come on It's a school night.
别做个臭婊子，过来
Don't be a needy bitch Get over here
好吧。待会见，我们一结束就
Okay. I'll see you soon We'll come over
过去，再见。爱你
as soon as it's over Okay, bye. Love you
我听到你叫你的朋友过来
I heard you telling your friends to come over here
你会抽一些大麻 - 不，才不是
and you're gonna smoke some weed -  No. No
那个阿拉卡萨姆？ - 朱利安，我说的是，
That Alakazam? - Julian, I'm talking about,
比如，呃，你知道的，比如，一个魔术，
like, uh, you know, like, a ma-magic trick,
像嘛咪嘛咪哄 - 我知道你在说话
like, abracadabra. - I know you're talking
关于吸大麻的事不要骗我
about smoking weed Don't lie to me
这破坏规则了，我要告诉我妈妈
That's against the rules I'm telling my mom
好吧，我会告诉你妈妈你浏览器历史记录的事
Well, I'm gonna tell your mom about your browser history
你最好别这样 - 你给我添堵
You better not - You can get me in trouble,
我也不让你痛快 - 我
I can get you in trouble - I'm
你曾经是我最喜欢的，但你现在是
You used to be my favorite, but now you're,
打个比方，我看着的第十喜欢的小孩
like, my tenth favorite boy that I nanny
我照顾的都是一些他妈的loser小屁孩
And I babysit some fucking loser kids
如果我有其他类型的保姆，
If I had some other kind of babysitter,
她会给我读一个故事
she'd be reading me a story
那样我就不会去剪我那讨厌的脚趾甲
I wouldn't be up clipping my nasty-ass toenails
嗯。上床睡觉 - 你以前很好的
Uh-huh. Go to bed  - You used to be cool
我们以前是朋友，但现在
We used to be friends But now
好吧。抓紧，去睡觉
Okay. Come on, go to bed
- 等一下 - 已经过了你的就寝时间
- Wait - It's way past your bedtime
你想成为一个好孩子？- 嗯
You want to be a good kid? - Mm-hmm
嗯。- 去睡觉，去睡觉，- 你得到多少报酬？
Mm-hmm. - Go to bed, go to bed - How much do you get paid?
来吧，睡觉去，我们走
Come on, let's go, let's go
我抓住你了。快走
I'll get ya. Come on
晚安，小伙子
Good night, little dude
嘿，维基
Hey, Vicky
你能把门开着吗？一个门缝就行？
Can you leave the door open? Just a crack?
好的
Yeah
晚安
Good night
顺便说一下，你实际上是我做保姆最喜欢的孩子
By the way, you're actually my favorite kid I babysit for
我也喜欢你
I like you, too
晚安
Good night
那不是
That is not what
操。好吧，真的
Fuck. Okay, that really
那把我坑了，好吧
that fucked me up. Okay
艾莉森！
Allyson!
艾莉森，过来！
Allyson, come here!
等等。嘿，艾莉森，- 不，那是怎么回事？
Wait. Hey, Allyson - No. What was that?
好吧，哪个？什么？嘿，- 那是什么？
Okay, what? What? Hey, - wh What was that?
什么？这是什么？
What? What's this?
什么？老兄，有一些判断力，好吗？
What? Dude, have some discretion, all right?
我不知道你以为你看到了什么，
I don't know what you thought you saw, but, like,
i...金真的只是在和我说话
I... Kim literally was talking to me
真的吗？她向我走过来，
Really? She came up to me and, like,
在我耳边低语，好吗？
whispered in my ear, okay?
你没必要因为这事就哭
You don't have to cry about it
没什么大不了的
It's not that big a deal
是奥斯卡惹到你了么？- 不，不
So Oscar got you fucked up? No, I got
我是说，我搞砸了。i
I mean, I got me fucked up. I
行了
Okay
嘿，好吧，我们能谈谈吗？好吧，- 不要
Hey, okay, can we just talk? Okay - Don't
好吧，这里，你知道吗？不
Okay, here, you know what? No
你他妈的贵重的手机？
Your fucking precious phone?
他妈的怎么了？
What the fuck?
你会明白吗？
You gonna get that?
或者你想让我得到它？
Or you want me to get it?
等...等等，等等，等等
Hold... hold up, hold up Wait, wait, wait
我们结束了
I'm done
这是手台14
This is Unit 14
我在米勒老太太家外面哦，妈的
I'm out by Old Lady Miller's house Oh, shit
我在这里没有看到任何可疑的东西，完毕
I don't see anything suspicious out here. Over
呃，10 - 4你想继续么，呃，
Uh, ten-four You want to go ahead and, uh,
代码2号，正式取消
show yourself code two, officially cancel
请求援助？
request for assistance?
嗯，是的。完毕
Uh, affirmative. Over
哦，妈的
Oh, shit
抱歉嗨
Sorry Hi
我不想按门铃吵醒孩子
I didn't want to ring the doorbell and wake up the kid
没关系，看看，我刚做好的
It's okay Check it out. Fresh from my patch
哦，我的上帝，- 他的眼睛是心形的
Oh, my God  - His eyes are hearts
我喜欢- 是吧
I love it - Yeah
我是泰特・哈罗。- 嗨，泰特
This is Tate Hello. - Hi, Tate
你好。怎么了？嗨。你好吗？
Hello. What's up? Hi. How are ya?
我们拥有整栋房子吗？
Do we have the whole house to ourselves?
是这么回事么？ - 是
Is that how this works? - Yes
真棒，直到艾莉森和卡梅隆来到这里
Sweet Until Allyson and Cameron get here
好吧，所以，在此期间，你想做些爆米花
Okay, so, in the meantime, you want to make some popcorn
看恐怖电影？
and watch a spooky movie?
嗯，不，- 好吧，等等，看看这个
Mm, no  - All right, wait, check this out
你会喜欢这个的
You're gonna like this
我去
I went
纹了这个纹身
and got this tattoo
因为今夜是就是那一夜
because tonight is the night,
这是我们余生都会记得的
the one we'll remember for the rest of our lives
你今晚会被榨干的
You are so getting dry-fucked tonight
哦，是吗？他妈的来吧
Oh, yeah? Fuckin' come here
什么？
What?
那是什么？什么？
What was that? What was what?
你听到什么了吗？
Did you hear something?
不，怎么了？
No. What was it?
我不知道。我想
I don't know. I thought
我想我听到了什么声音之类的
I thought I heard, like, a noise or something
是啊，可能只是朱利安在屙屎
Yeah, it's probably just Julian taking a dump
你去看看好吗？
Would you go look?
一定要去么
Do I have to?
是的，你能去看看吗？
Yeah, would you please go look?
行
Okay
很奇怪好吧
It was weird All right
好吧，小伙伴
All right, little buddy
哦，干！ - 我看见有人在走廊上，
Oh, fuck me！ - I saw someone in the hallway,
就站在我家门外
standing outside my door
哦，怎么了，伙计？
Oh What's up, buddy?
有一张死脸，从黑暗中看着我
There was a fucked-up face, watching me from the dark
鬼和妖怪，小伙伴？
Ghosts and goblins, little buddy?
闭嘴，戴夫！我听到他的呼吸声，
Shut up, Dave! I heard him breathing,
然后我看见了他他在这里
and then I saw him He's in here
夜魔在这房子里
Boogeyman's in this house
好吧。好吧，来吧，我懂了
Okay. All right Come on, I got you
我们区看看，- 让戴夫先去
Let's check it out  - Send Dave first
不，没关系。没事，不，不，不，有关系
No, it's fine. It's fine No, no. No, it's not
没关系。来吧， - 不，不是。不，不是
It's okay. Come on  - No, it's not. No, it's not
来吧，告诉我你在哪里看到了夜魔
Come on, show me where you saw Boogeyman
我会保护你的。我很强壮。我保护你 - 不
I'll protect you. I'm strong. I got you - No
不，维姬，你先上去，- 我会把他打出去
No, Vicky, you go up there first - I'll fight him off
来吧。我保证 - 不
Come on. I promise  - No
你能给我妈妈打电话吗？好的
Can you call my mom? Yeah
如果房间里有什么东西，我会打电话给她
If there's something in the room, I'll call her
他就站在那里――在门里
He was standing right there in-in the door
我去看看
I'll check it out
对不起，先生
Excuse me, sir
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing in here?
拜托，请离开这
Please, you need to leave
请离开
Please leave
维基？
Vicky?
现在就出去！
Get out now!
吓到你了吧 - 你他妈的在开玩笑吗？
Gotcha - You fucking kidding me?
你很安全
You're safe
这里什么都没有
Nothing's in here
你确定？嗯
You sure? Mm-hmm
你检查窗帘后面了么？
Y-You check behind the curtains?
我检查了整个房间
I checked the whole place
干啊
Sick
看到了吗？没什么好害怕的
See? There's nothing to be afraid of
这里没有什么夜魔
There's no Boogeyman in here
如果是洋娃娃怎么办？
What if it's a doll?
哦，可能是，比如，一个奇怪的，小娃娃，
Ooh, it could be, like, one of those weird, like, kid dolls,
一个奇怪的婴儿，他们盯着你
one of those weird babies, and they stare at you
用那双闪亮的小眼睛
with those beady little eyes
救命！戴夫！
Help! Dave!
帮我！
Help me!
维克！
Vicky!
哇！
Whoa!
朱利安，快跑！
Julian, run!
我去找人帮忙。戴夫！戴夫！维基？
I'll go get help. Dave! Dave! Vicky?
快跑！
Get out of here!
不要上去！戴夫，你会被杀的
Don't go up there! You're gonna get killed, Dave
谁来帮我！
Somebody help me!
戴夫，帮我！维姬
Dave, help me! Vicky
不，不，不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no, no
不，不，不
No, no, no
不！不！
No! No!
去他妈的
Fuck this
各单位，我们有报告
All units, we have reports
子午线大道707号的家庭骚乱
of a domestic disturbance at 707 Meridian Avenue
请回答。完毕
Please respond. Over
收到，总台
Copy that, Dispatch
好了，伙计们，别忘了说谢谢
Okay, guys, don't forget to say thank you
来吧，够了。不，来吧
Come on That's enough. No, come on
不，他们可以多吃一点，亲爱的
No, they can have a little more, honey
不给糖就捣蛋，闻闻脚汗不汗
Trick or treat, smell my feet,
给我一些好吃的
give me something good to eat
哈登菲尔德公安局的！
Haddonfield Sheriff's Department!
针对家庭骚乱！
Responding to a domestic disturbance!
我重复一遍，这是霍金斯警官
I repeat This is Officer Hawkins
请回复
Please respond
亲爱的，小心！
Honey, watch out!
从这里给我消失！现在！
Get out of here! Now!
走吧，伙计们。快走
Let's go, guys. Move
看起来像个傻
and looks like an idiot
然后我看起来也像个傻比给他辩解
And then I look like an idiot for vouching for him
进去！
Get inside!
操！
Fuck!
迈克尔！
Michael!
哦，妈的
Oh, shit
劳丽。操！
Laurie. Fuck!
天啊，弗兰克！
Jesus Christ, Frank!
靠！他妈的怎么了？
Fuck me! What the fuck?
你来这干嘛?
What the hell are you doing here?
弗兰克，他在这里
Frank, he's here
我知道
I know
请这边走
This way, please
看看谁来了
Look who's up
他在哪里？
Where is he?
你告诉我
You tell me
迈克尔放倒了警卫和司机之后
The bus lost control after Michael
巴士失去控制了
overtook the first guard and the driver
他不再休眠了
He's no longer dormant
他只知道如何继续前进
He only knows how to keep moving
继续杀戮
and to keep killing
除非他被捕，否则他会再次杀人
And he will kill again unless he's captured
跟我来一会儿
Come with me for a minute
你坐着别动
You sit still
嗯，我是坐着不动的啊
Well, I was sitting still anyway
什么意思? - 留着他有用
What do you mean? - He's an asset
他没用，他是个累赘
He's not an asset He's a liability
不，不，他也得参与行动
No, no. He's on this hunt
没有人比他更了解迈尔斯
Nobody knows Myers better than he does
哦，谢谢你， - 你要我带着
Oh, thank you - You want me to take
这个受伤的平民要去寻找
this injured civilian to go look for
精神病连环杀手？警长
a psychopathic serial killer? Sheriff
弗兰克。我们在做什么？
Frank. Wha-What are we doing?
劳丽，我们现在不需要你的帮助
We don't need your help right now, Laurie
你就这么傻站着！快做点什么！
You're just standing here! Please do something!
对不起，警官们
Excuse me, officers
劳丽・斯特罗德
Laurie Strode
劳丽・斯特罗德，见见萨丹医生
Laurie Strode, meet Dr. Sartain
我是迈克尔的医生
I'm Michael's doctor
兰比尔・萨尔坦
Ranbir Sartain
哦，你是新的卢米斯
Oh, you're the new Loomis
我读过你和迈克尔的一切
I read everything about you and Michael
一切
Everything
你认识我们的朋友霍金斯吗
Did you know our friend Hawkins here
是第一个应诉代理人
was the first responding deputy
迈克尔在1978年被捕的时候？
when Michael was apprehended in 1978?
那天晚上，他阻止了卢米斯杀死迈克尔
He stopped Loomis from killing Michael that night
你知道我每天晚上祈祷
Do you know that I pray every night
他会逃跑吗？
that he would escape?
你干嘛这么做？
What the hell do you do that for?
这样我就可以杀了他
So I can kill him
好吧，这是为愚蠢的事情祈祷
Well, that was a dumb thing to pray for
我相信他会道歉的，他只是需要睡一觉
I'm sure he'll apologize He just needs to sleep it off
卡梅伦不想让任何人看到他是个坏人，
Cameron doesn't want anyone to see him as a bad guy,
但是后来他喝醉了，变得好斗
but then he gets drunk and gets belligerent
我真厌倦了每个人都让我失望的生活
I'm really tired of everybody letting me down all the time
你应该得到更好的
You deserve better
我是说
I mean
艾莉森，你最酷，最漂亮，
Allyson, you're the coolest, you're the prettiest,
你是学校里最好的女孩
and you're the nicest girl in school
如果有人不欣赏这一点，
And if anyone doesn't appreciate that,
那他一定是个疯子
they're a crazy person
谢谢你
Thank you
你真暖心
That's very sweet
让我们离开这里
Let's get out of here
我知道一条捷径
I know a shortcut
从临床角度来看，
From a clinical perspective,
医生，你会说劳丽・斯特罗德
Doctor, would you say that Laurie Strode
失去理智了么？
has lost her fucking marbles?
悲剧和暴力有很多方式
There are many ways for tragedy and violence
改变受害者
to change a victim
他们会逐渐习惯担惊受怕
They can grow accustomed to always being afraid,
在不断的恐惧中
in constant fear
他们可能会变软弱，也可能会变强
They can grow weak, they can grow strong
但也有另一面
But there's also the other side
什么另一面？
What other side is that?
对凶手的影响
The effect on the victimizer
你看，这就是吸引我的地方
You see, this is what has intrigued me
通过我的研究
through my studies
像迈克尔这样的犯罪对他有何影响？
How does a crime like Michael's affect him?
嗯？那是什么感觉？
Hmm? What's that feeling?
他是随机的，还是情绪化的
Is he on a random path, or is he emotionally driven?
是什么触发的？
Triggered by something?
也许是一些闻所未闻的行军命令
Perhaps some unheard marching order
印在他的灵魂里
imprinted on his very being
我想知道他的感受
I want to know what he's feeling
我想知道他从杀戮中得到什么快乐
I want to know what pleasure he gets out of killing
凶手在哪里？我们必须找到他
Where is this killer? We gotta find him
这次我不会妨碍公正正义了
I'm not gonna stand in the way of justice this time
记住，他是国家财产
Remember, he's property of the state
他不能受到伤害哦 - 是吗？
He mustn't be harmed -  Oh, yeah?
走着瞧吧
We'll see about that
这里不安全
It's not safe here
艾莉森在哪里？
Where's Allyson?
她在哪里？
Where is she?
艾莉森在哪里？！
Where's Allyson?!
亲爱的，我是妈妈，你能在收到信息
Honey, it's Mom Can you please call me back
一刻立马给我回个电话么，求你了
the second that you get this, please?
警察说他们撤离了舞会，
The police said that they evacuated the dance,
我联系不上你
and I can't get in touch with you
他们要我们去你外婆家
And they're making us go to your grandmother's house
那边是安全的
because it's safe
甜心，我是你外婆
Sweetheart, this is your grandmother
有一名警察在你家等着把你
There is a police officer waiting at your house
带到我们身边
to bring you to us
小心所有毒常春藤
Watch out for all the poison ivy
别让我掉在上面 - 没问题，我抓住你了
Don't let me fall on that  - All right. I got you
我抓住你了。好了，我抓住你了好了，走吧
I got you. Okay, I got you Okay, go
哦！行
Oh! Okay
你做到了。耶
You did it. Yay
干得不错
Good job
耶
Yay
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我的意思是，你应该得到更好的
I mean, you deserve better
对吧？我是说 - 不
Right? I mean - No
你他妈怎么回事？
What the fuck?
我...那什么？你反正不再和卡梅隆在一起了
I-I... What? You're not with Cameron anymore
这并不
That does not
这并不意味着我想和你在一起
That does not mean I want to be with you
我以为...我以为你在给我暗示呢
I thought... I thought you were sending me signals
绝B没有信号这回事 - 我很抱歉
Definitely no signals - I'm so sorry
拜托，你不能告诉卡梅伦这件事
Please, you cannot tell Cameron about this
我什么也没感觉到。我发誓
I-I didn't feel anything, either. I swear
我没有...等等，我没有。你真可怜
I didn't... Wait, I didn't You are so pathetic
我要回家了，你可以自己搞清楚状况
I'm going home. You can figure your own shit out
嘘...谁在那里？什么...嘿！
Sh... Who's there? Wha-What... Hey!
运动传感器，傻吊！
Motion sensor, dumb-ass!
艾莉森，我，
Allyson, I'm, like,
真的喝醉了，真的
really drunk right now Seriously
我在派对上非常兴奋，就像，
I got really horny at the party, and, like,
所有这些女孩都在我身上跳舞
all these girls were, like, dancing on me
阿廖森，他们美丽的身体让我大吃一惊
Their beautiful bodies got me all chubbed out, Allyson
我..阿廖森，求你了！
I... Allyson, please!
哦，操，那是...哦！
Oh, fuck, that was... Oh!
啊~sharia
Ah, sharia
你能关上壁橱门吗？
Uh, c-could you close the closet door?
是
Yeah
哦，他妈的！
Oh, shit!
哦，天哪
Oh, God
不！
No!
哦！
Oh!
我们会在一起的
We're all gonna be together
现在，照我说的做
Now, do as I say
哦，妈的
Oh, shit
这玩意真危险
It's treacherous as hell here
好吧，你还好吗？
Okay You good?
扶着我的手
Take my hand Okay
在这儿 - 这是有史以来最愚蠢的捷径
Right here - This is the dumbest shortcut ever
他们，就像他们喂我吃鳄梨酱一样
They, like they were feeding me guacamole
以及其他性感的方式
in all these sexy ways
这不是我的~
It's not my
万圣节快乐，埃尔罗德先生，我只是
Happy Halloween, Mr. Elrod I'm-I'm just
我不知道，伙计。对不起
I don't know, man. I'm sorry
我不想跑进你的院子拉屎之类的，伙计
I'm not trying to trespass on your yard and shit, man
我只是想走捷径
I was just trying to take a shortcut
和一个非常漂亮的女孩在一起，我只是
with a really pretty girl, and I just
我真的很喜欢她，伙计，
I just really like her, man,
我原以为她也喜欢我
and I-I thought that she liked me, too
我只是...只是
And I just... it just
你真的喜欢过一个女孩吗
Have you ever really liked a girl
可你就是不能拥有她？
and you just couldn't have her?
我是...对不起，伙计
I'm s... I'm sorry, man
我只是...我会安静的离开的，伙计
I'll just... I'll peace out of your hair, man
谢谢-谢谢你
Thank-thank you for
嘿，呃
Hey, uh
你去哪了，伙计？你在演戏么
where'd you go, man? You're acting
伙计，你在演戏，好像
Dude, you're acting, like,
很浮夸 我不
really sketchy right now I don't
呃
Uh
怎么了？
What's up?
我...我...我要走了，我不
I'm-I'm-I'm leaving right I don't
我是
I'm
噢！哦，我的上帝！啊！啊！
Ow! Oh, my God! Aah! Aah!
救命！救命！
Help me! Help!
求你了！有人么！
Please! Somebody!
来人啊，救命啊！
Somebody, help me, please!
来人，求你了！拜托，有人！
Somebody, please! Please, somebody!
一切都会好起来的
Everything's going to be okay
妈妈，我很抱歉
Mom, I'm so sorry
我试图阻止他来这里
I tried to stop him from coming here
好吧。行
Okay. Okay